The AFC Champions League Elite 2025-2026 resumes with eight teams from the West Zone in contention.
亚冠精英联赛2025-2026重燃战火 西区将有八支球队卷入争夺之中
to secure a place in the quarterfinal of the centralized tournament.
他们只为在集中赛制的1/4决赛中占据一席之地
With defending champions Al-Oli Saudi FC and former winners Al-Hilal, Essie,SFC, Al Sadis C and Al Etihad Club in the
卫冕冠军阿奥利沙特FC 以及前冠军阿尔希拉尔 埃西SFC 阿萨迪斯C 阿尔艾蒂哈德俱乐部同场混战
mix,
局势愈发扑朔迷离
the four single leg round of 16 ties are set to be blockbuster affairs.
接下来四场单回合16强对决注定会是场场重头戏
com previews the four tantalizing matchups.
比赛前瞻也为你奉上四组令人心动的对阵
Winners of the inaugural AFC Champions League Elite last season.
上赛季首届亚冠精英联赛的冠军
Saudi Arabia's Al-Oli will be eyeing a similar run this time around after another prolific league stage campaign.
阿奥利这次同样瞄准类似的冲击 在又一段高产的联赛阶段征程之后
where they finished second in the West Zone standings.
他们在西区积分榜上最终排名第2
Matthias Jaisel's side suffered only one defeat in the eight matches,
马蒂亚斯·贾伊塞尔的球队在8场比赛里只遭遇1次失利
winning five and drawing two to pick up 17 points.
赢下5场 2场打平 拿到17分
of Qatar, will be determined to provide a challenge
来自卡塔尔的这支队伍 也将誓要掀起挑战
despite a seventh-place finish in the league stage.
尽管联赛阶段只排在第7位
Campaign for the Jamal Belmody-led side, who advanced despite losing 3-2 to Araxal's shorter SC in their final league stage
由贾马尔·贝尔莫迪率领的球队在最后一轮联赛阶段虽以2-3不敌阿拉克斯尔短途SC 但仍挺进晋级
match.
凭借那场比赛的结果
Belmody, however, will draw confidence from the 2-2 stalemate against Al-Oli in the league stage
不过 贝尔莫迪将从联赛阶段对阵阿尔-奥利2-2的顽强战平中获得信心
as they target a place in the last eight. For the first time since 2022,
当他们目标是跻身八强之际
with Adil Boubina the joint tournament leading scorer with six goals,
这是自2022年以来的首次——
just like they did in the 2024-2025 season.
而且阿迪尔·布拜纳以6球并列赛事头号射手
Saudi Arabia's Al Hilal Al-Assad.LSFC were imperious in the league stage,
就像他们在2024-2025赛季那样
topping the West zone with 22 points.
沙特阿拉伯的阿尔希拉尔·阿尔-阿萨德——LSFC在联赛阶段势不可挡
with a goalless draw against UAE's Shabab Al-Oli being the only blip in an otherwise flawless run.
他们以22分力压西区
Simone Nzoghi's first season at the club saw the four-time Asian champion sparkle
而与阿联酋沙巴布·阿尔-奥利0-0握手言和 几乎是他们完美之旅中唯一的瑕疵
and secure their place in the knockout stage with three matches to spare.
西蒙妮·恩佐吉在加盟后的首个赛季让这支四度夺得亚冠的队伍闪耀生光
Qatar's Al-Sad endured a tumultuous league stage campaign.
并在还剩三轮的情况下提前锁定淘汰赛席位
with their spot in the round of 16 only secured on the final matchday
卡塔尔的阿尔-萨德经历了一段动荡不安的联赛征程
thanks to Sharjah FC's 2 - 1 defeat to PFC Nassau.
他们进入16强的席位 直到最后一轮才最终敲定
Having started their campaign with Felix Sanchez in charge,
全靠沙迦FC以2-1不敌PFC纳索
Italian Roberto Monchini has since taken over. But their recent form has not been good.
在费利克斯·桑切斯执教期间开启本届征程后
and they will have to be at their best to deny Al-Hilal,
意大利人罗伯托·蒙钦随后接过教鞭 但他们近期状态并不理想
who defeated them 3 - 2 in the league stage.
他们在联赛阶段以2-1击败了对手
Islamic Republic of Iran's Traktor FC were the surprise package of the West Zone league stage.
伊朗伊斯兰共和国的特拉克托尔FC堪称西区联赛阶段的最大冷门
Finishing third, level on 17 points with Al-Oli
他们以第三名收官 与阿尔-奥利同积17分
as they sealed a round of 16 place with two matches to spare.
并在还剩两场的情况下就锁定了16强席位
The ultra-tight defense they've had has been the bedrock of their campaign.
他们那种极为紧凑的防守 正是整个征程的根基
with experienced goalkeeper Ole Reza Berimbang having kept a tournament leading five clean sheets.
经验丰富的门将奥莱·雷扎·贝里班明曾连续保持全场零封 整届赛事前五场都做到了零失球
Shabab Al-Oli of the United Arab Emirates had a decent league stage campaign.
来自阿联酋的沙巴布·阿尔-奥利在联赛阶段表现也相当不错
having won three matches and drawn two to finish in sixth spot on 11 points.
他们赢下3场 战平2场 最终以11分排名第六
Paulo Souza's side relied on the goalscoring prowess of Bruno,
保罗·索萨的球队 主要依靠布鲁诺的进球能力
who has four goals, and the silky skills of Guilherme Bola.
他个人有4球 还有古尔梅雷·博拉那手细腻的技术
With both Brazilians capable of unlocking any defence on their day.
两名巴西人只要当天状态在线 就都有能力撕开任何防线
It was a 1 - 1 draw when Traktor and Shabab met in the league stage,
特拉克托尔和沙巴布在联赛阶段交手时 双方战成1-1
and this tie promises to be another evenly fought affair.
而这次对决也同样有望势均力敌
Saudi Arabia's Al-Ittihad will be raring to go after five wins
沙特阿拉伯的阿尔-伊蒂哈德在豪取5场胜利之后士气正盛
took them to a fourth place finish in the league stage on 15 points.
他们最终以15分收获联赛第四名
Sergio Cancicao's arrival at the club sparked a revival
塞尔吉奥·坎塞考的加盟点燃了球队的复苏
as they ended their league stage campaign strongly with three straight wins,
因为他们在联赛阶段后程强势收官 连胜三场
scoring 12 goals in the process.
并在此过程中打进12球
Leading their charge will be attacking midfielder Hausa Mawa,
在进攻端领衔的将是进攻型中场哈乌萨·马瓦
who has six goals in his hand, while Moussa Diaby has five assists to his name.
他目前已收获6球 而穆萨·迪亚比则贡献了5次助攻
UAE's Alwada FC only finished a rung lower and a point adrift of their opponents,
阿联酋的阿尔瓦达FC仅比对手低一名 并且少一分
proving their capability with memorable wins along the way.
用一场场令人难忘的胜利证明了自己的实力
One of those was the 2 - 1 success against Al-Ithihad on matchday one,
其中一场是在首轮2-1击败阿尔伊蒂哈德
when Lucas Pimenta struck a last - gasp winner to give Darko Milani a fantastic start to their campaign.
卢卡斯·皮门塔在最后时刻打入制胜球 为达尔科·米兰尼的征程开了个绝佳头彩
Revenge will be on the minds of Al-Ithihad as they seek a third continental title.
当阿尔伊蒂哈德力争拿下第三座洲际冠军时 复仇的念头势必在他们心中萦绕
The AFC Champions League Elite 2025-2026 goes into hyperdrive
亚冠精英联赛2025-2026正式进入高强度模式
as the West Zone's eight teams bid to stay in the hunt for the ultimate prize in Asian club football.
因为西区的8支球队将全力争取 守住通往亚洲俱乐部顶级荣誉的希望
So expect plenty of thrills and spills from the four matches.
因此 接下来的四场比赛就别错过了精彩与刺激
Stay updated on the action through the AFC's digital platforms.
通过亚足联的数字平台持续关注比赛动态
And don't forget to download the AFC Live app on the Apple App Store and Google Play for live scores.
别忘了在Apple App Store和Google Play下载AFC Live应用 实时比分尽在掌握
Results, news and more.
赛果 新闻和更多精彩